worldboxingnews.net 2014-10-01

# World Boxing News - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which World Boxing News collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.worldboxingnews.net/ website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by World Boxing News.  

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information

World Boxing News may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

\- To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Changes to this privacy policy

World Boxing News has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us

 _ **If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:**_  
 _ **  
**World Boxing News

 _7 Old Smithy Lane_  
 _Lymm_  
 _Warrington_  
 _Cheshire_  
 _WA13 ONW_

 _Or for a swifter response at ** **_

_ _ **[phildjay@worldboxingnews.net](mailto:phildjay@worldboxingnews.net)**_

This document was last updated on June 30, 2014

Privacy policy created by http://www.generateprivacypolicy.com
